zicasso.com 2019-03-20

# Zicasso Privacy Policy | Zicasso

This Privacy Policy was last updated: February 26, 2007

Thank you for visiting Zicasso, Inc.'s ("Zicasso") Internet web site ("Site") located at the URL zicasso.com. This Privacy Policy details certain policies implemented throughout Zicasso governing Zicasso's use of personally identifiable information about users of our Site and users of our services on this Site ("Services").

## Privacy Policy Updates

Due to the Internet's rapidly evolving nature, Zicasso may need to update this Privacy Policy from time to time. If so, Zicasso will post its updated Privacy Policy on our Site located at www.zicasso.com and we may send registered users an email, so you are always aware of what personally identifiable information we may collect and how we may use this information. If any modification is unacceptable to you, you shall cease using this Site and the Services. If you do not cease using this Site and the Services, you will be deemed to have accepted the change.

## Information Collection

You can generally visit our Site without revealing any personally identifiable information about yourself. However, in certain sections of this Site and when you use our Services, we may invite you contact us with questions or comments or request information and complete a registration form or submit trip requests and/or trip plans. Due to the nature of some of these activities, we may collect personally identifiable information such as your name, e-mail address, physical address, telephone numbers, login ID, password and other contact information that you voluntarily transmit with your emails or other communications to us.

## Information Use

We may use your personally identifiable information for the following purposes:

  * Registering you to use our Services;
  * Providing you with notices regarding goods or Services that you have purchased or may wish to purchase in the future;
  * Contacting you to deliver certain Services or information you have requested;
  * Providing you with targeted advertising;
  * Ensuring the technical functioning of our network;
  * Protecting your account from unauthorized access and verifying your authority to enter the Site;
  * Developing new services and improving the content and general administration of the Site and our Services; and
  * Improving the quality and design of the Site and Services to create new features, promotions, functionality, and Services by storing, tracking, and analyzing user preferences and trends

In addition, when you send email or other communications to Zicasso, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our Services.

If you opted to receive communications from Zicasso such as promotional e-mails and newsletters when you registered to use the Site and the Services but subsequently wish to cease receiving communications, we encourage you to indicate your preference to unsubscribe or opt out from receiving such communications by updating your account in accordance with the Updating, Correcting and Deleting Personally Identifiable Information section below.

## Trip Requests and Trip Plans

The Site is a business-to-consumer travel site that facilitates relationships between travel companies ("Travel Companies") and potential consumers who want to purchase travel services ("Travelers"). A Traveler submits information to the Site about travel services that the Traveler is interested in purchasing (each, a "Trip Request"), to which a Travel Company can submit a proposal to such Traveler ("Trip Plan"). Other Site users can see the content of a Trip Request, however, only Travel Companies can see the username of the Traveler associated with such Trip Request.  
Profile Pages, Photos, Message Boards, Feedback, Ratings, Comments, and Public Forums

As part of your account, you may create a profile page and upload photos and post travel logs. Any personal information or content that you voluntarily disclose online (in feedback, ratings and comments, etc.) becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by others.

Your username (not your email address) is displayed on the Site to other Site users when you upload photos, post feedback and/or comments or send messages through this Site. Therefore, if you associate your name with your username, then Site users to whom you have revealed your name will be able to personally identify you through your activities on the Site.

## Data Integrity

Zicasso processes personal information only for the purposes for which it was collected and in accordance with this Privacy Policy. To the extent necessary for such purposes, we review our data collection, storage and processing practices to ensure that we only collect, store and process the personal information needed to provide or improve our Services. We take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we process is accurate, complete, and current, but we depend on our users to update or correct their personal information whenever necessary.

## Cookies

We may use small text files called cookies to improve overall Site experience. A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Cookies generally do not permit us to personally identify you.

## Aggregate Information

The Site may track the total number of visitors to our Site, the number of visitors to each page of our Site, browser type, IP addresses, External Web Sites (defined below) linked to, and we may analyze this data for trends and statistics in the aggregate, but such information will be maintained, used and disclosed in aggregate form only and it will not contain personally identifiable information. We may use such aggregate information to analyze trends, administer the Site, track users' movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.

## Disclosure

We may provide your personally identifiable information and the data generated by cookies and the aggregate information to the vendors and service agencies that we may engage to assist us in providing our Services to you. For example, we may provide your personally identifiable information to a Travel Company in order to assist them to submit a Trip Plan in response to your Trip Request. We will also disclose your personally identifiable information (a) if we are required to do so by law, regulation or other government authority or otherwise in cooperation with an investigation of a governmental authority, (b) to enforce the Zicasso Terms of Use agreement or to protect our rights or (c) to protect the safety of users of our Site and our Services. We will not sell your personally identifiable information to any company or organization except we may transfer your personally identifiable information to a successor entity upon a merger, consolidation or other corporate reorganization in which Zicasso participates or to a purchaser or acquirer of all or substantially all of Zicasso's assets to which this Site relates.

## Links to Third Party Sites

The Site may provide links to other Web sites or resources over which Zicasso does not have control ("External Web Sites"). Such links do not constitute an endorsement by Zicasso of those External Web Sites. You acknowledge that Zicasso is providing these links to you only as a convenience, and further agree that Zicasso is not responsible for the content of such External Web Sites. Your use of External Web Sites is subject to the terms of use and privacy policies located on the linked to External Web Sites.  
Security

We may employ procedural and technological measures that are reasonably designed to help protect your personally identifiable information from loss, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction. Zicasso may use firewall protection, password protection, internal restrictions on who in Zicasso has access to your personally identifiable information and other security measures to help prevent unauthorized access to your personally identifiable information.

## Updating, Correcting and Deleting Personally Identifiable Information

Zicasso provides you with the ability to review, correct and update your personally identifiable information that you provide to us by accessing and modifying this information on your profile page or by submitting a request to us by e-mail to: [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#2a424f465a6a5043494b59594504494547).

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy please contact us at the email address set forth above.

Our computer systems are currently based in the United States, so your personal data will be processed by us in the U.S. where data protection and privacy regulations may not offer the same level of protection as in other parts of the world, such as the European Union. If you create a user account with the Site as a visitor from outside the United States, by using the Site you agree to this Privacy Policy and you consent to the transfer of all such information to the United States, which may not offer an equivalent level of protection of that required in the European Union or certain other countries, and to the processing of that information as described in this Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy is effective as of: February 26, 2007
